wbrz.com 2018-06-30

# WBRZ News 2 Louisiana : Baton Rouge, LA | Privacy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience, while using our service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identification information, including but not limited to CAMERA, RECORD_AUDIO, READ_PHONE_STATE, GET_ACCOUNTS. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy. The mobile app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

**For Privacy Concerns Please Contact Our Privacy Hotline**

**Phone:** 225.387.2222  
**Fax:** 225.336.2344  
**Email:** [privacy@wbrz.com](mailto:privacy@wbrz.com)[](mailto:humanresources@wbrz.com)

We will make every effort to respond or otherwise resolve your inquiry within 24 hours or 1 business day.

**Written Privacy Complaints Should Be Directed to the Following:**

**Privacy Complaints**  
1650 Highland Road Road  
Baton Rouge, LA 70802  
Email: [privacy@wbrz.com](mailto:privacy@wbrz.com)

Before sending a formal written complaint, we recommend you first contact our privacy hotline. We may be able to resolve your problem immediately without the need for a formal complaint. In any event, we will respond to your complaint within 30 days.
